http://www.seedsavers.org/privacy

Privacy PolicyWe respect your privacy and will attempt to ensure that personal information about you is handled responsibly.In order to access certain materials or services on this site, you may be asked to provide your name, address, phone number or other information. It is your decision to provide this information. We will only use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please be advised that you may opt-out of receiving certain information from Seed Savers Exchange. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this web site.Browsing our websiteYou can browse www.seedsavers.org without telling us who you are (but please don't be a stranger). The information we collect from a typical web site visit (one that does not involve a form submission or online store checkout) is your IP address, the pages you view and the date and time you view them. We use this information to measure site and store activity in order to improve the usefulness of our website to our visitors. We also use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reports to better understand who is visiting our site in order to improve its features and functions for you. This information is based on Google Advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers and is only used in aggregate (we don't tie this to an individual). To learn more about the use of this information and to opt-out, please visit https://support.google.com/ads/?hl=en#topic=2971788 or https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/Email SubscriptionsIf you’ve given us your express consent, we also send our email newsletter to your email address. This consent can be withdrawn or modified at any time by following the Manage Preferences link at the bottom of every marketing email. Please note that even if you update your consent, you will continue to receive transaction-based emails about orders you place. Please contact us if you wish to remove your email address or any other information completely from our system. If you place future orders on our site, you are agreeing to our terms and privacy policy. Collection of personally identifiable informationVisitors must register in order to use certain features of our website, such as our online shop, Send a Note web form, forum, blog, webinars, or email newsletters. During registration, you are asked to provide contact information such as name, email address, or zip code. We use this information to verify the authenticity of your email, and we may on occasion contact you about features and services that we believe may be of interest.When you shop at our online store, we request information that enables us to respond. This information could include contact information (such as name, shipping and billing address, phone and email address) and, if applicable, financial, payment, or billing information. Visitors who create an account with us have the ability to create and maintain their own password. That password is encrypted so we cannot see what it is. If you provide us with your credit card information, it is also encrypted within our e-commerce system.We may gather email addresses and other personally identifiable data about visitors when such data is voluntarily submitted to www.seedsavers.org. For example, our site uses submission forms for visitors to sign up for a free catalog; request information; or to sign-up for our newsletters. Other contact information (e.g., mailing address, phone number) may be used to verify your order, customer or membership information, or to contact you about opportunities with Seed Savers Exchange that we feel may be of interest to you. Financial information is used to bill you in connection with your order. Seed Savers Exchange cannot insure against invasion by security breakers of any manner.We make every effort to ensure the secure collection and transmission of sensitive user information using industry-accepted data collection and encryption methodologies.We do not sell, share, rent or trade your information.CookiesA cookie is a small data file stored on a visitor's computer that contains information about the visitor. Like most websites, SSE may place a cookie in the browser files of a visitor's computer. We use persistent cookies to store your information when you sign-in to your account so that you will not have to re-enter it when you visit again. We also use transient cookies to store items in your online store shopping cart. If visitors decline to accept cookies, they may still use our site, but some portions of our site may be inaccessible.Use of Location DataWhen you access this web site on a mobile device, we may determine your current location and use that information to help you find nearby retail stores who sell our products. We do not share your location information with any third parties, nor do we use it for any purpose other than to determine your distance from the stores. If you are not comfortable with this, you may disable the use of location services in the application settings at any timeDisclaimersAffiliationsSeed Savers Exchange, Inc. is not affiliated with the Facebook group Seed Savers Exchange Group. Both of us support biodiversity through preserving, growing, and sharing heirloom seeds and plants.
